<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Covid19 Voca AI</string>
    <string name="covid19_description">
        The project, Corona Voice Detect, was created for early diagnosis of COVID-19 (Coronavirus).
        It combines recently developed AI and voice forensic technologies, finding specific
        patterns in voice, tone and other sounds that we produce as we speak, that relate
        to unique illnesses and other human factors.
        \n\n
        But first we need your help! We need to curate recordings from both healthy individuals
        and those tested positive for Coronavirus in order to gather enough data for consumer use.
        Please record your voice daily and reply to a few questions to help us fight this illness!
        Make your mark and become a part of this historic journey by helping us diagnose and slow
        the spreading of Coronavirus and bring remote testing to every human in the world at NO EXPENSE!
    </string>

    <string name="project_info">
        Corona Voice Detect, is led by Dr. Shmuel Ur a renowned Israeli inventor and Dr.
        Alan Bekker,CTO &amp; Co-founder at Voca.ai. The success of this project will have an
        immense impact on the health of our communities and prevention in spreading.
        \n\n
        We’re starting with global data collection. With this data, we will be able to identify
        and develop technologies to determine the probability of being infected with the virus
        from voice analysis. The research and development effort is being conducted in
        collaboration with Professor Rita Singh from Carnegie Mellon University, and other
        researchers worldwide. Researchers will use this data to study and develop algorithms
        that will automatically detect COVID-19 and related illnesses from voice. These will
        potentially serve as rapid tests that can be performed over a phone or computer, and
        aid in the diagnosis of Coronavirus.
    </string>

    <string name="success_phase">Following the success of the data collection phase,
        people will soon be able to determine the likelihood of contracting the virus – with
        just one short voice recording. NOW THAT SOUNDS REMARKABLE!!!
    </string>

    <string name="made_by">Made with ❤️ By Omer Elimelech</string>
    <string name="omer_tkd_gmail_com">omer.tkd@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="re_record">Tap to Re-record</string>
    <string name="select_option">Select %s</string>

    <string name="gender">gender</string>

    <string name="cels">Celsious</string>
    <string name="Fahrenheit">Fahrenheit</string>

    <string name="centitmeters">Centimeters</string>
    <string name="feet">Feet</string>

    <string name="select_one_option">Select one option</string>

    <string name="have_diagnosed_conditions">Have you been diagnosed with any of the following conditions?</string>

    <string name="height_in_centimeters">height in centimeters</string>

    <string name="select_country">Select country</string>

    <string name="were_you_diagnosed">Were you diagnosed with COVID-19?</string>


    <string name="smoke">smoke</string>
    <string name="diagnoses">Diagnoses</string>
    <string name="current_status">Current Status</string>
    <string name="sympthoms">Sympthoms</string>

</resources>
